const translateQuestions = [
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Life", answer: "Жизнь" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Milk", answer: "Молоко" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Cow", answer: "Корова" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Soap", answer: "Мыло" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Longbottom", answer: "Долгопупс" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Sun", answer: "Солнце" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Raining cats and dogs", answer: "Ливень" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Monkey", answer: "Обезьяна"  },
  { question: "Translate in russian:", formula: "Batman", answer: "Илья Муромец" },
  { question: "Translate in russian:",  formula: "Philosopher's stone", answer: "Филосовский камень"}
];
export default translateQuestions;
